[{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664091522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":14311,"timeElapsed":106438},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664100348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":8824,"timeElapsed":115264},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664113177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":12827,"timeElapsed":128093},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664127951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":14773,"timeElapsed":142867},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664140981,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":13029,"timeElapsed":155897},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664153714,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":12731,"timeElapsed":168630},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664163840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":10125,"timeElapsed":178756},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664168893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5052,"timeElapsed":183809},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664179020,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":10125,"timeElapsed":193936},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664206825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":26390,"timeElapsed":221740},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664213693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6868,"timeElapsed":228609},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664225308,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":11614,"timeElapsed":240224},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664231125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5815,"timeElapsed":246041},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664236611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5485,"timeElapsed":251527},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664245880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":9267,"timeElapsed":260796},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664253856,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":7975,"timeElapsed":268772},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664258498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4641,"timeElapsed":273414},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664265448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":6949,"timeElapsed":280364},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664280516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":13343,"timeElapsed":295432},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664289046,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":8529,"timeElapsed":303962},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664297087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":8040,"timeElapsed":312003},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664302031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":4942,"timeElapsed":316947},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664315916,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":13884,"timeElapsed":330832},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664319611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3694,"timeElapsed":334527},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664326163,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":6551,"timeElapsed":341079},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664330790,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":4626,"timeElapsed":345706},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664334605,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3815,"timeElapsed":349521},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664350325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":14041,"timeElapsed":365241},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664355421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":5095,"timeElapsed":370337},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664369311,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":13889,"timeElapsed":384227},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664375081,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":5768,"timeElapsed":389997},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664390418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":15337,"timeElapsed":405334},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664394841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":4422,"timeElapsed":409757},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664400798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5955,"timeElapsed":415713},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664407963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":7164,"timeElapsed":422879},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664411633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":3669,"timeElapsed":426549},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664423157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":10278,"timeElapsed":438073},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664429688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":6530,"timeElapsed":444604},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664436475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6786,"timeElapsed":451391},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664440720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4243,"timeElapsed":455636},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664450326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":9606,"timeElapsed":465242},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664455600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":5273,"timeElapsed":470516},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664466592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":10990,"timeElapsed":481508},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664470220,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3627,"timeElapsed":485136},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664476836,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":6615,"timeElapsed":491752},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664492993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":14973,"timeElapsed":507909},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664496607,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3613,"timeElapsed":511522},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664501445,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4838,"timeElapsed":516361},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664504157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2710,"timeElapsed":519073},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664508942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":4783,"timeElapsed":523857},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664512585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":3642,"timeElapsed":527501},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664519840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":7254,"timeElapsed":534756},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664523580,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3739,"timeElapsed":538496},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664532062,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8480,"timeElapsed":546978},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664544592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":12529,"timeElapsed":559508},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664555932,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":10085,"timeElapsed":570848},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664560924,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4991,"timeElapsed":575840},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664568397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7471,"timeElapsed":583313},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664572681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4283,"timeElapsed":587597},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664579876,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":7193,"timeElapsed":594791},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664584855,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":4979,"timeElapsed":599771},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664589923,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":5066,"timeElapsed":604839},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664594976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":5051,"timeElapsed":609892},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664598742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3765,"timeElapsed":613658},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664611368,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":11631,"timeElapsed":626284},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664616231,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4861,"timeElapsed":631147},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664623688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":7456,"timeElapsed":638604},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664627558,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3869,"timeElapsed":642474},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664632927,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":5368,"timeElapsed":647843},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664636965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4034,"timeElapsed":651881},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664641304,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":4333,"timeElapsed":656220},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664647502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":6192,"timeElapsed":662418},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664650796,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3291,"timeElapsed":665712},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664664226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":11727,"timeElapsed":679142},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664668603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":4376,"timeElapsed":683519},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664678193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":9588,"timeElapsed":693109},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664683913,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5718,"timeElapsed":698829},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664691855,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":7941,"timeElapsed":706771},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664708347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":16490,"timeElapsed":723263},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664712383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":4034,"timeElapsed":727299},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664720078,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":7695,"timeElapsed":734994},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664724356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4276,"timeElapsed":739272},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664727863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":3506,"timeElapsed":742779},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664739568,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":10501,"timeElapsed":754484},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664745088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5518,"timeElapsed":760004},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664753709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":8620,"timeElapsed":768625},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664759202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5491,"timeElapsed":774118},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664764500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5297,"timeElapsed":779416},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664767338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2836,"timeElapsed":782254},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664772511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5172,"timeElapsed":787427},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664777807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":5295,"timeElapsed":792723},{"subjectID":"3gndak67bp","prolificID":"66eb24d93cf3e118289817f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215d9ca0db6f8b78d1e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664781088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3279,"timeElapsed":796004}]